frontlinenews.in 2014-03-15

# Privacy & Terms | Frontlinenews

## Privacy Policy for Frontlinenews.in 

We are very happy and appreciate you for joining our social bookmarking network service. Please read this below user agreement that will give you a very clear understanding about our terms and conditions fully & completely before you submit a story for a posting contributor.

Our social Bookmarking Website is made of Pligg Content Management System. 

Our website provides friendly, enjoyable

We are only service based website . Our social bookmarking - service based website free and easy way to promote their websites which is very helpful for SEO Devlopement keywords to improve and to boost search engine rankings.

We invite world wide visitors to use our social bookmarking service with and unique and a quality content.

We are very strict about illegal/bad words such as porn, alcohol, drinking, guns, weapons, gambling etc.., please don't submit this types words in our websites.. we will remove this kind of words if we notice it and we close the membership too. 

## **Important:**

**Moreover, we are not responsible any kind of user submitted content by our users in our website which may be copy content, copy-right, illegal or about brand and etc.**

 **If you find any type of links that are illegal or copyright please inform us so that we can remove them from my website immediately. But we are not responsible for that type of links in our websites.**

At thebookmarktimes.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by thebookmarktimes.com and how it is used. 

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, thebookmarktimes.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons 

thebookmarktimes.com does not use cookies. 

## DoubleClick DART Cookie 

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on thebookmarktimes.com. .:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to thebookmarktimes.com and other sites on the Internet. .:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .... Google Adsense Adf.ly Infolinks Propellerads

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on thebookmarktimes.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

thebookmarktimes.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. thebookmarktimes.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
